http://www.joinmyband.co.uk/privacy.php

Add us on Google+
×Coronavirus (Covid-19): We would like to take this opportunity to send our thoughts to all our Join My Band users. We urge you all to stay at home and stay safe; make plans for the future when all of this has passed. Take this time to write more music and maybe work on an online/virtual collaboration with someone in another part of the country you may not have otherwise jammed with. But please follow government advice, stay at home and stay safe.
Home > Privacy & Cookie Policy
Privacy & Cookie Policy
Join My Band are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
(1) What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation);
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;
(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters
(e) any other information that you choose to send to us;
(2) Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on the website.
The following cookies are set that are required to ensure functionality of core features of our website:
PHPSESSIDPurpose: to maintain your user sessionExpires: end of session
joinmyband_sidPurpose: to maintain your current logged in user sessionExpires: end of session
joinmyband_tPurpose: track whether a topic has unread posts during your user sessionExpires: end of session
joinmyband_dataPurpose: to keep user logged into our websiteExpires: 1 year
versionPurpose: to remember your preference for your current session if you have chosen to view our full site on a mobile device rather than our mobile versionExpires: end of session
cookie_noticePurpose: to detect whether the cookie notice has been shownExpires: 1 year
existingPurpose: to detect whether this is your first visit to our website to serve you the most optimised version of our CSS Expires: 1 year
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at:
http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
The following cookies are set by Google Analytics.
__utmaPurpose: Identify unique visitors to the siteTypical content: Randomly generated numberExpires: 2 years
__utmbPurpose: establish and continue a user session on the siteTypical content: Randomly generated numberExpires: 30 minutes
__utmcPurpose: Used to determine session statusTypical content: Randomly generated numberExpires: end of session
__utmzPurpose: Used to track traffic sources and page navigation.Typical content: Randomly generated number & info on how the visitor found the siteExpires: 6 months
For more information on the cookies set by Google Analytics please visit this page. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.
We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: https://adssettings.google.com/. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin. Find out more about how Google uses information from sites or apps that use their services here: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
For more information on cookies and how to manage them, please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org/.
You can manage your personalised advertising privacy settings here:Update your advertising tracking preferences
(3) Using your personal information
Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a) administer the website;
(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;
(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(j) provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
(k) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
If you would like to delete your Join My Band account you can do so using the "Delete your account" page found in the "My Account" section of the website.
All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, PayPal. You can review the PayPal privacy policy at www.paypal.com. We will share information with PayPal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments.
(4) Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose your personal information:
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling; and
(e) to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5) Security of your personal information
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).
(6) Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
(7) Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:
(a) the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity.
We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.
You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email at any time. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.
(8) Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(9) Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(10) Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to support@joinmyband.co.uk.
Latest Featured Ads
Double bassist and drummer needed for rockabilly trio (London/Surrey) Looking to jam with a drummer. (Manchester) Ballistic UK looking for drummer (Leicester) BLUES DRUMMER wanted! (Essex) BASS WANTED FOR FUNK ROCK BAND (WIRRAL/LIVERPOOL)
Looking for band members?
Advertise on Join My Band for FREE and find musicians in your area!
Copyright © Join My Band 2020. All rights reserved. Terms of Use | Privacy & Cookie Policy.
